All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
After a change of plans, Horty threatens to crush the entire island under the weight of a massive ship.
Erase our past! Set us back to zero! Eradicate the shadows cast by our grudge so that we may see the light!
All we can do is start over! We must!
Brother Hoshi, just let me do this my way! Trust me!
Our minds were made up as soon as we got to the plaza.
With Jimei's help, we were gonna save this island!
Leave it to me and my crew!
That's what friends are for, right?
Try your best, but I'll catch you long before you reach the Gnome!
What should we do, Luffy?
You'll be okay! Just follow my lead and I promise I won't let Horty hurt you!
Yes! Right!
Luffy's all-out attack! Red Hawk Blasts!
The Rusty Preston
Whoa!
Oh, my God!
Ugh!
Wait, that's odd.
But that's stripey fellow go.
I've completely lost sight of him.
Uh, come on, where is he?
And where is he?
Imbecile, I'm right here!
But you'll be dead long before you can notice.
Now take this!
Camouflage carpet!
Why did it sound like the ground was talking?!
Wow, that's some good aim.
Zeo!
You've fallen into my trap.
Little did you know that was my weapon destroying technique, Body Sword Crush.
Now the tip of your sword has crumbled.
It's worthless!
No, I stabbed you.
He really thinks he can play it off!
Your arrogance will only lead to your defa- uh, lead to your defeat!
Did he just say defa-
Shh!
He'll hear you!
Fumbled over your words there a little, huh?
Hey!
Shut up, you dumb head!
Huh?
What?
I lost him again!
How does he do that?!
Do that!
Hidden flail!
Huh?
Sixty-six, now!
I've learned something in these past two years.
I've come to an understanding about the true nature of the revive, revive fruit.
When most people die, their body is left behind while their soul continues on to the next world.
But my soul is different.
In accordance with the power of my devil fruit, it has been tempered like iron.
Radiating with strength, it maintains its hold in this realm with a presence that is palpable.
That soul resonates through the strings of my instruments.
Rock and roll, screaming from another dimension.
Mesmerized by its melodies, the listeners dance their way into a land of illusions.
But when my soul flutters away from this old body, it is no mere apparition.
It can be seen as surely as my rattling bones.
I did it!
Popped his head right off his bony neck!
I killed a straw hat!
I'm fine.
You can chop me up as much as you'd like.
For it is neither flesh nor organs that bind me to this world.
So what is it that gives me life, you might ask?
It's my soul!
What?
I killed him so hard it brought him back to life.
Man, I'm good!
Are you for real?
Is it starting to sink in yet?
Keep it up.
But none of your attacks can damage these bones of mine.
I'm already dead and you're not going to kill me twice.
Also, this blade I wield is like none other, sharpened by the long-armed tribe and granted up a fitting name.
Soul Solid!
Engrave that title upon your heart!
With a single soulful slash, it'll freeze you with the frigid air creeping from the land of the dead.
As its icy grip claims you, gaze upon its bitter blade!
Nice, Brook!
That's awesome!
You sounded like a total badass!
I'm a big Soul King fan now!
Oh, yeah!
Goodness, well thank you, Usopp!
Oh, crap!
Really?
You'd think I would've learned to keep my eyes on him by now!
I guess I'd better step it up.
The whole crew's looking good.
Showing off those skills they learned for the new world.
Yeah, yeah!
It's real sweet to hear how highly you think of all your friends!
But don't you worry, since I'm such a nice guy, I'll make sure to drown all of you together!
Special attack!
Fireball cutter!
Here comes Green Star!
Green Star!
And Green Star!
Bouncing faster!
I think it's safe to say I found the weak link in the Straw Hat crew.
All those shots and you couldn't even hit me a single time!
Ka-ka-ka!
Huh?
Might wanna stay put, Mole Shark!
I'm a cookie cutter shark, jerk!
Whatever.
I hope you enjoy the trap I set for you.
Look Luffy!
Horde is heading right for us!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
So you think you're gonna protect everyone on the island?
Well, let's see you try! Show me what you got!
Ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Suck it, Gear!
And Gum-Gum!
Shad!
Head to G Jacob!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Rawr!
You call that a punch?
A movie?
It's pointless, Straw Hat.
Don't you get it yet?
The heavens endowed us with this power.
We can't lose.
Just lie down and give up.
You can't stop the Noah now,
and you'll watch every one of your friends perish.
Hell no!
I'm putting you down!
Delusions of grandeur.
Now, die!
Second gear! Armament!
I swear I'll never let anyone I love die again!
Now, come come!
Come on, I'm gonna bite your arm off.
Red Hawk!
I not.
Don't think we'll put this in place.
I Youtube and respect.
End of show.
Getting trivia connects us so a lot of people schwierig to get to see good minds!
There are already for questions out there!
You have to do this мой hands on my power arm.
It's not my god persuasive.
It's totally possible.
Muyiguang with your SERVICEIA.
Or they...
The number one is rigging me.
gema colon sounds to me and physics 1983.
problema Ever.
Sometimes people in energy we heb to dress up real limits Beige is a hatchet.
You did it, Luffy!
Straw Hat!
He won!
Straw Hat Luffy did it, he defeated the captain of the new Fishman Pirates, Hordy is down!
He really did it, he really stopped him, we're gonna be safe!
Jay, this isn't over yet!
Wiffy Hoshi, let's get to the NOAH!
Right!
Full speed ahead!
Okay!
What?
That's impossible!
Captain Hordy lost the fight?
But how?
You're kidding me!
What about the NOAH?
This is the end!
Everyone on the island is doomed!
Run for it!
Why, Zeo?
The island's gonna get crushed!
Please let us go!
Don't you dare fall for it!
You know the power our captain has!
He was chosen by HEAVEN!
He could never be beaten by some measly pathetic human!
But, I mean, we're not getting nothing if the NOAH destroys this place!
Death is only another form of revenge!
And we will die for our hatred of humans!
Our flesh and blood will be remembered as a tragedy!
And the grudge against humans will grow ever stronger!
We may fall, but thousands more will stand up to take revenge in our name!
Oh, goody!
There you are!
You're all insane!
Not just Captain Hordy, but all of you officers too!
Blame the humans!
They're the ones who made us this way!
Don't run!
Take that rage of yours, and let it loose on all of humanity!
They deserve your hate!
Look around!
Do you know what they've done to us?!
They're the ones behind every disaster the fishmen have met!
Is all that stuff you're saying true?
Are humans really that bad?
Huh?
No way!
That's ridiculous!
I mean, sure!
Humans have done plenty of awful things!
Especially when you look at their history with-
That's enough!
Huh?
Madam Charlie!
You can see what's happening with your own eyes!
Just look!
On the ground!
And in the sky!
The humans are fighting against the new fishman pirates!
For us!
What about that guy?
Is he human?
Their crew is a bit strange!
But the important thing is what they're doing!
You must see things for yourself!
That's the only way to understand the truth!
No matter what you've heard in the past,
you must look at today with an objective eye!
Even if you refuse to fight to the death and try to run,
I'll kill you myself!
Your hatred of humans won't be wasting!
Huh?
They're your own people!
That's how you treat them?!
I almost died!
Thank you so much, Mr. Skeleton Mask!
You again, huh?
You've never died!
So don't talk like you know anything about it!
Die to leave your hate behind?
That's just absurd!
There's nothing left when you die!
The only things left behind are your bones!
The guy knows what he's talking about!
Thank you!
If there's one kind of person I don't like,
it's someone who doesn't value the lives of others!
I can't even stand their smell!
AND I DON'T HAVE A NOSE TO SMELL THEM!
You and your friends are the ones who don't value the lives of others!
I bet you all think you're being bold and selfless by staying here to fight,
but every last one of you humans are gonna die when the Noah hits the island!
Although I'm still not sure whether you're human or not!
I can promise you that one of these days our Captain Luffy will become the king of the pirates!
He is a man who keeps his word no matter the cost!
So if he says that no harm will come to the people here, then no harm will come!
I believe in him no matter what!
So that ship will never touch this island!
And now it's time for me to step up and do my part!
That means I won't let you disappear before my eyes again!
Even though I have no eyes to speak of!
Grillo!
Whoa, how about this?
Impressed yet?
Oh sure, that's pretty damn big!
Yeah! Impressive stuff!
Not so!
Well then, do you want to wrap this up now, Jinbei?
Jinbei?
Yeah, it's about time.
Hey, not fair.
You've destroyed both of my swords.
How can I win a sword fight if I don't have swords?
Not my problem.
All right, I'm going balls out.
This new special move is going to take you down in a single shot.
One, two, and on the third step, it's all over.
Think I'm kidding?
Just try me.
What kind of moron do you take me for?
I'm calling you out on your stupid bluff.
You're a weakling and you'll always be a weakling.
You know, I used to lie about this kind of stuff all the time.
But now it doesn't really matter if you believe me or not.
Because I know I'm the real deal.
Holy crap!
What is that monster?
Where did that thing come from?
Whoa, did he?
No, not again.
Huh?
That runt?
How'd he get so big?
Whoa, pal!
Easy!
Calm down, Chopper!
You can't lose control like before!
Don't worry, Usopp!
I know what I'm doing!
pay rep!
Oh!
what's wrong?
it's...
look!
It's...
Horny!
What's wrong?
It's... there... look!
It's Hordy!
He can still stand?
Are you ready?
Let's go!
I can breathe!
I can't breathe!
You know...
I can't believe it!
Yeah, it's fabulous happened.
The Straw Hat crew pushes forward with all of their might, aiming to end the battle with the
new Fishman Pirates once and for all. Horty takes more energy steroids, robbing Luffy of time that
he can't afford to spare. Luffy, gravely injured and running out of strength, struggles to overcome
the Fishman's superhuman stamina. On the next One Piece, coming to an end, the final decisive battle
against Horty. I'm going to be King of the Pirates!